http://www.marsdenjacob.com.au/privacy-policy

Speak with us
We’ll explain more over the phone than this website ever could
General Enquiries
+61 3 8808 7400
Or tell us briefly what you need and the right person will call you back.
Name
Phone
What can we do for you?
Submit
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Speak with the right person
We specialise in developing bespoke solutions for bespoke issues.
The best way to find out if we are right for your needs is by speaking to the right person. So, skip the website and let’s talk. You can find the right person to speak with using the lists below.
Sectors
Any Sector
Water
Energy & Clean Energy
Agriculture & Earth Resources
Environment & Climate Change
Transport
Public Policy
Richard Wrightson
Search results:
Nadja Arold
Water , Public Policy , Environment & Climate Change , Non-market valuation , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform , Quantitative methods & modelling , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Investment appraisal & business cases
Call
Email
Connect
Evan Branosky
Water , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Governance & institutions
Call
Email
Connect
Dr Joel Byrnes
Transport , Public Policy , Water , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Andrew Campbell
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Rod Carr
Water , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Transport , Other Sectors , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Non-market valuation , Investment appraisal & business cases , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Dr Jeremy Cheesman
Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Water , Other Sectors , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Non-market valuation , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Matthew Clarke
Transport , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Public Policy , Water , Environment & Climate Change , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Due diligence , Investment appraisal & business cases , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Richard Clarke
Public Policy , Other Sectors , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Market design
Call
Email
Connect
Lachlan Dawson
Water , Environment & Climate Change , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Non-market valuation , Investment appraisal & business cases , Strategy design , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design , Governance & institutions
Call
Email
Connect
Grant Draper
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Investment appraisal & business cases , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Gavan Dwyer
Agriculture & Earth Resources , Public Policy , Water , Environment & Climate Change , Transport , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Makere Hurst
Public Policy , Transport , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Environment & Climate Change , Water , Non-market valuation , Investment appraisal & business cases , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Peter Jacob
Water , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Public Policy , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Philip Jones
Public Policy , Investment appraisal & business cases , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design
Call
Email
Connect
Kanchana Karunaratna
Water , Public Policy , Environment & Climate Change , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Investment appraisal & business cases , Strategy design , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Non-market valuation , Quantitative methods & modelling , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Dr Peter Kinrade
Environment & Climate Change , Energy & Clean Energy , Public Policy , Strategy design , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Non-market valuation
Call
Email
Connect
Nina Lewis
Call
Email
Connect
Amanda Ley
Water
Call
Email
Connect
Stuart Maclachlan
Agriculture & Earth Resources , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Water , Governance & institutions , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Alex Marsden
Agriculture & Earth Resources , Public Policy , Environment & Climate Change , Water , Transport , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Non-market valuation
Call
Email
Connect
Dr John Marsden
Call
Email
Connect
Peter McKenzie
Energy & Clean Energy , Market design , Policy design , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Gabriela Medina
Call
Email
Connect
Dr Veronika Nemes
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Water , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Quantitative methods & modelling , Investment appraisal & business cases
Call
Email
Connect
Rob Nolan
Water , Energy & Clean Energy , Transport , Public Policy , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Investment appraisal & business cases , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Alasdair Norton
Call
Email
Connect
Katie Pawlik
Call
Email
Connect
Hana Ramli
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Quantitative methods & modelling , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Amy Rogers
Investment appraisal & business cases , Non-market valuation , Quantitative methods & modelling , Market performance & evaluation
Call
Email
Connect
Dr David Rogers
Water , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Quantitative methods & modelling , Investment appraisal & business cases , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform , Market performance & evaluation
Call
Email
Connect
Philippa Short
Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Investment appraisal & business cases , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform , Market performance & evaluation
Call
Email
Connect
John Smith
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Public Policy , Water , Other Sectors , Transport , Governance & institutions , Policy design , Policy evaluation & reform , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery
Call
Email
Connect
Rick Stankiewicz
Water , Energy & Clean Energy , Transport , Public Policy , Investment appraisal & business cases , Regulation, pricing & cost recovery , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform , Market performance & evaluation , Strategy design , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Simo Tervonen
Water , Agriculture & Earth Resources , Public Policy , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Due diligence , Policy design , Governance & institutions , Policy evaluation & reform
Call
Email
Connect
Richard Wrightson
Energy & Clean Energy , Environment & Climate Change , Due diligence , Strategy performance evaluation & reform , Strategy design , Market design , Market performance & evaluation , Quantitative methods & modelling
Call
Email
Connect
Click below to view full list of specialists.
More Specialists
Speak to the right person
Scroll to top
